Inventory of the Richard Throssel Papers, 1900-1993 (bulk 1902-1933)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Photographs and Negatives, 1902-ca. 1920s; Series I.; 14.86 cubic ft. (6 letter boxes, 1 F24 box, 39 negative boxes, 5 shoe boxes and 4 F20 boxes).
  - Celluloid/Glass Negatives and Photographs, Subseries III.
    - Hill Covered in Snow (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1377
    - Hill Covered in Snow (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1378
    - Snow Drift (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1379
    - Snow Drift (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1380
    - Snow Drift (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1381
    - River in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1382
      Negative Box 48
    - River in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1383
    - Path Covered in Snow (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1384
    - Tree Grove in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1385
    - Snow Drift (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1386
    - Snow Covered Opening in Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1387
    - Mountain Covered with Patches of Snow (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1388
    - Man Hunting in Mountains (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1389
    - Men Overlooking Canyon (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1390
    - Canyon with Dead Trees in Bottom (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1391
    - Mountain with Scarce Vegetation (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1392
    - Mountain with Scarce Vegetation (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1393
    - Mountain Prairie (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1394
    - Mountain Prairie (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1395
    - Canyon Wall (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1396
    - Canyon Wall (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1397
    - Canyon Wall (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1398
    - Canyon Wall (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1399
    - Canyon Wall (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1400
      Negative Box 46
    - Canyon Wall (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1401
    - Road on Side of Hill (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1402
      AHC Neg. #25172
    - Path Lined with Trees (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1403
      AHC Neg. #25173
    - Cottonwood Trees (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1404
    - Brush (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1405
    - Women on Horseback (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1406
    - Parade in Billings(?), Montana (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1407
    - Parade in Billings(?), Montana (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1408
    - Parade in Billings(?), Montana (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1409
    - Parade in Billings(?), Montana (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1410
    - Parade in Billings(?), Montana (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1411
    - Parade in Billings(?), Montana (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1412
    - Stagecoach in Parade (Box 6, Folder 9)
      TP1413
    - Covered Wagon in Parade (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1414
    - Covered Wagon in Parade (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1415
    - Man Leading Pack Mules in Parade (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1416
    - Stagecoach Being Hitched Up (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1417
    - Man Leading Wagon (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1418
    - Stagecoach Loaded with People (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1419
    - Stagecoach Loaded with People (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1420
    - Stagecoach Moving (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1421
    - Stage Holdup (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1422
    - Stage Holdup (Box 6, Folder 10)
      TP1423
    - "Bucking Mule, Casper Fair" by R.R. Doubleday (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1424
    - "Calgary Red on Sky Rocket" by Doubleday - Foster Co. (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1425
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1426
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1427
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1428
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1429
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1430
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1431
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1432
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 11)
      TP1433
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1434
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1435
      1 glass negative 3 x 4
      1 glass positive 3 x 4
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1436
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1437
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1438
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1439
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1440
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1441
      1 celluloid negative 5 x 7
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1442
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1443
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1444
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1445
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1446
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1447
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1448
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1449
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1450
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1451
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1452
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1453
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1454
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1455
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1456
    - Bronco Riding - "McDowell of Pryor No.12" (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1457
    - Bronco Riding - "Litzsinger of Billings No.13" (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1458
    - Bronco Riding - "Herman Venerable of Miles City No. 1" (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1459
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1460
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1461
    - Bronco Riding - "Collins of Miles City No. 6" (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1462
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1463
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1464
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1464A
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1465
    - Bronco Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1466
    - Bull Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1467
    - Bull Riding (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1468
    - "Chester Byers, Roping, Pendleton, Oregon" (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1469
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1470
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1471
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1472
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1473
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1474
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1475
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1476
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1477
    - Roping (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1478
    - "Guy Schults, Bulldogging" 1920 Doubleday (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1479
    - Bulldogging (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1480
    - "#8 Lynch Bulldogging - Miles City Roundup" by D.F. Photo Co. (Box 6, Folder 12)
      TP1480A
    - Bulldogging (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1481
    - Bulldogging (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1482
    - Woman Trick Rider (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1483
    - Woman Trick Roper (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1484
    - Woman Dismounting Horse (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1485
    - Woman Remounting Horse (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1486
    - Cowgirl (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1487
    - Cowgirl (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1488
    - Cowgirl (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1489
    - Trick Roper (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1490
    - A Trick Roper (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1490A
    - Riders (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1491
    - Saddling Horses (Box 6, Folder 13)
      TP1492
    - Horse Racing (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1493
    - Horse Racing (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1494
    - Horse Racing (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1495
    - Horse Racing (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1496
    - Men Trying to Handle Horses (Wild horse race) (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1497
    - Horse Falling Down with Man on Top (Wild horse race) (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1498
    - Men Showing Pack Horses (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1499
    - Men Showing Pack Horses (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1500
    - Men Loading Horses onto Boxcars (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1501
    - Man Working on Horse in Holding Pen (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1502
    - Wagons with Horseback Riders in Long Line (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1503
    - Grandstands Full of People (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1504
    - Horse with Indian Saddle (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1505
    - Photographer Running from Bull (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1506
    - "The 'Ford' of the Early Settler of the West" 1917 D.F. Photo Co. (Box 6, Folder 14)
      TP1507
    - Cattle Skull (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1508
    - Cattle Skeleton (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1509
    - Man with Pack Mules (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1510
    - Man with Pack Mules - Teton Mountains in Background (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1511
    - Cowhands Eating Around Campfire (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1512
    - Cattle Drive Crossing River (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1513
    - Men and Wagon in Front of Small Cabin (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1514
    - Man on Horse (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1515
    - People and Wagons Near Ranch Buildings (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1516
    - Man Fording River (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1517
    - Two Cowhands - One on Horseback (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1518
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1519
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1520
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1521
      Negative Box 47
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 15)
      TP1522
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 16)
      TP1523
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 16)
      TP1524
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 16)
      TP1525
    - Cattle (Box 6, Folder 16)
      TP1526
    - Horses in Stockyard (Box 6, Folder 16)
      TP1527
    - Man Holding Horse (Box 6, Folder 16)
      TP1528
    - Horses in Mountain Setting (Box 6, Folder 16)
      TP1529
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1530
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1531
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1532
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1533
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1534
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1535
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1536
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1537
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1538
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1539
    - Downtown Street Scene (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1540
    - Airplane (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1541
    - Airplane (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1542
    - Airplane (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1543
    - Airplane (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1544
    - Airplane (Box 6, Folder 17)
      TP1545
    - Street Scene at Night (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1546
    - Horses (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1547
    - Street Scene (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1548
    - Country Scene with Car (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1549
    - Country Scene with Car (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1550
    - River Dam (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1551
      AHC Neg. #25174
    - River Dam (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1552
    - Flood Gate (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1553
    - Flood Gate - Water Exploding in to Air (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1554
    - Indian Delegation Meeting Train (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1555
    - Passenger Car Loaded with Shriners (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1556
    - Train Wreckage (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1557
    - Train Engine (Box 6, Folder 18)
      TP1558
    - "Joella Irwin - A.F.P. Co." - Cowgirl (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1559
    - Cowgirl on Horse (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1560
    - Cowgirl on Horse (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1561
    - Cowgirls (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1562
    - Cowgirls "Rene Hafley, Fox Hastings, Rose Smith, Ruth Roach, Mable Strickland, Prairie Rose, Dorthy Morell" Doubleday Photo (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1563
    - Rifle Shooting (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1564
    - Rifle Shooting (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1565
    - Rifle Shooting and Motorcycle Rider (Box 6, Folder 19)
      TP1566
    - Boy Fishing (Box 6, Folder 20)
      TP1567
    - Man Fishing (Box 6, Folder 20)
      TP1568
    - Man Fishing with Boy Watching (Box 6, Folder 20)
      TP1569
    - Two Boys Fishing (Box 6, Folder 20)
      TP1570
    - Man Fishing (Box 6, Folder 20)
      TP1571
    - Two Men Fishing in Canyon (Box 6, Folder 20)
      TP1572
    - Two Men Fishing in Canyon (Box 6, Folder 20)
      TP1573
    - Two Men Fishing (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1574
    - Two Men Fishing (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1575
      3 print
    - Boy Fishing with Net (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1576
    - Girl Fishing (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1577
    - Girl Fishing (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1578
    - Man Fishing (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1579
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1580
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1581
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1582
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1583
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1584
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1585
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1586
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 21)
      TP1587
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1588
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1589
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1590
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1591
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1592
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1593
    - Motorcycle Race (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1594
    - The Alamo (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1595
      1 celluloid negative 3½x 4½
    - The Alamo (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1596
    - The Alamo (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1597
    - The Alamo (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1598
    - Two Men Walking Through Mission (The Alamo) (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1599
    - Mission (The Alamo) (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1600
    - Photographer with Car (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1601
    - Photographer with Car (Box 6, Folder 22)
      TP1602
    - People with Car (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1603
    - People with Car (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1604
    - Car Loaded with Equipment (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1605
    - Mountain Ranch and Car Loaded with Equipment (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1606
    - Mountain Ranch and Cabin (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1607
    - Mountain Cabin (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1608
    - Mountain Cabin (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1609
    - Mountain Cabin (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1610
    - Mountain Cabin (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1611
    - Farm House (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1612
    - Farm House (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1613
    - Farm House (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1614
    - Farm House (Box 6, Folder 23)
      TP1615
    - Woman Wrapped in Sheet (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1616
    - Woman Wrapped in Sheet (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1617
    - Woman Wrapped in Sheet (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1618
    - Woman Wrapped in Sheet (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1619
    - Woman in Nightgown on Bed (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1620
    - Nude Woman On Bed (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1621
    - Nude Woman Back View (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1622
    - Nude Woman in Stream (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1623
    - Nude Woman in Stream (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1624
    - Nude Woman in Stream (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1625
    - Nude Woman in Stream (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1626
    - Nude Women in Stream (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1627
    - Women Standing in Road (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1628
    - Nude Indian Women in Stream - Photo of Painting (Box 6, Folder 24)
      TP1629
    - "Zimmerman Trail - Rimrocks, Billings," Montana (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1630
    - Man in Early Marine Uniform (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1631
    - Man in Early Marine Uniform Standing by Sign Post (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1632
    - Man in Early Marine Uniform Standing by Recruiting Truck (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1633
    - Field Marshal Foch in Group (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1634
    - "General Jacques, General Bias, Marshal Foch, General Pershing, Admiral Beatty - Kansas City, Mo - Nov. 1st 1921" Doubleday Photo (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1635
    - Soldier and Man at Train Platform (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1636
    - Hunter with Dead Elk (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1637
    - Man (Well Dressed) - Portrait (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1638
    - Two Men Sitting on Rock by Ledge (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1639
    - Three Black Children Playing on Ropes (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1640
    - Three Black Children Playing on Ropes (Box 6, Folder 25)
      TP1641
    - Man with Long Moustache Delivering Speech from Car (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1642
    - "Calamity Jane, Notorious Frontier Character, Gen. Crook's Scout" (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1643
    - Indians on Horseback (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1644
    - Indian Man with Woman (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1645
    - Indians in Circle (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1646
    - "This is Where We Stopped Last Evening(?) for Lunch" - Man Near Tipi (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1647
    - "Sitting Bull - Nayfore Studio of Mandan, ND - Gilcleat Negative" (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1648
    - Geronimo [?] (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1649
    - "Chief Big Nose" - Doubleday Photo (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1650
    - "Chief Red Fish" with Indian Woman - Rembrandt Studio Bismarck, ND (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1651
    - Indian Chief (Box 6, Folder 26)
      TP1652
    - Indian Woman - Rembrandt Studio (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1653
    - Indian Woman with Baby (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1654
    - Indian Crossing River (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1655
    - Cars - Aerial View (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1656
    - "Sakakawea (Sacajawea) Statue - Bismarck, ND - Finney's" (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1657
    - Cavalryman Statue (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1658
    - Cavalryman Statue (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1659
    - State Capitol Building (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1660
    - State Capitol Building (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1661
    - Tents Set Near River (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1662
    - Stone Building - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1663
    - Lightning Storm (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1664
    - "Conley's Lake - Mount Powell in the Distance" (Box 6, Folder 27)
      TP1665
    - Three Men on Street (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1666
      1 film strip clipping 1½ x 4
    - Three Men on Street (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1666A
    - African Children and Women Bathing in River (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1667
    - African Children and Women Bathing in River (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1667A
    - African Children and Women Bathing in River (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1667B
    - The Face in the Rimrocks (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1667C
    - Throssel at Soda Spring (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1668
    - "Throssel Movie Man" - Throssel with Camera and Indian on Horse (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1669
    - Throssel with Rifle (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1670
    - Vera Throssel's Baby Picture (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1671
    - "Our First Christmas Tree" - Alberta and Vera Throssel (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1672
      AHC Neg. #25175
    - Alberta and Vera Throssel at Christmas (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1673
      AHC Neg. #25176
    - Dick Hawkins in Warbonnet - Throssel's Grandson (Box 6, Folder 28)
      TP1674
    - Woman on Cliff Edge - Possibly Mrs.Throssel (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1675
    - Two Girls on Cliff (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1676
    - Three Girls on Cliff (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1677
    - Girl in Field (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1678
    - Three Girls in Field (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1679
    - Two Girls Sitting on Box (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1680
      1 celluloid negative ½ x 2
    - Girl with Turkey (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1681
    - Two Girls Wading in Stream (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1682
    - Four Girls Playing on Bridge (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1683
    - Three Girls Playing on Bridge (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1684
    - Three Girls on Porch (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1685
    - Woman in Tree Swing (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1686
    - Picnic with Car (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1687
      AHC Neg. #25177
  - Lantern Slides, Subseries IV.
    This series contains colored lantern slides of select Throssel images. Click here to view digitized copies.
    - "The Blacklodge Teepees" (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1688
    - The Mourner (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1689
    - The Outdoor Kitchen (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1690
    - Carries the War Staff (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1691
    - The Pemmican Makers (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1692
    - The Summer Camp (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1693
    - Painting the Sun Dancers (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1694
    - Baby Whitebear (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1695
    - The Water Carrier (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1696
    - Beyond the Little Big Horn (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1697
    - Tall White Man (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1698
    - Into the West (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1699
    - Initiatory (Medicine Tobacco Ceremony) (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1700
    - A Secluded Home (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1701
    - The Ford (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1702
    - Plenty Coups - Chief of the Crows (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1703
    - Pretty Bird (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1704
    - The Game of Arrows (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1705
    - Building the Medicine Lodge (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1706
    - The Medicine Man's Daughter (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1707
    - Little Wolf - Cheyenne - Brother-in-Law of Two Moons (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1708
    - Medicine Tobacco Initiation Ceremony (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1709
    - Entering the Medicine Lodge - Initiatory (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1710
    - The Indian's Medicine (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1711
    - The Sign of His Medicine (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1712
    - Wolf - Crow (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1713
    - A Blackfoot's Lodge (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1714
    - An Old Crow Warrior (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1715
    - Bobtailed Horse - Cheyenne (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1716
    - A Crow Dancer (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1717
    - Bull Goes Hunting - The Old Historian (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1718
    - Strikes One with a Lance (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1719
    - The Other Medicine (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1720
    - The Other Medicine (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1720A
    - The Muskrat Hunter (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1721
    - A Medicine Teepee (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1722
    - Horse Goes Ahead (Sioux) (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1723
    - Striking Bear (Sioux) (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1724
    - The Returning Warriors (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1725
    - The Parade of Victory (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1726
    - Dancing in the Firelight (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1727
    - Sunset in Camp (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1728
    - Snow Bound (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1729
    - After the Fight (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1730
    - A Trapper (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1731
    - A Cheyenne Trapper (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1732
    - The Old Medicine Lodge (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1733
    - At the Brook (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1734
    - Curley (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1735
    - Crazy Head (Cheyenne) (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1736
    - Where Twilight Falls (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1737
    - Night (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1738
    - The Campfire (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1739
    - Moonlight on the Little Big Horn River (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1740
    - White Arm - Crow Chief (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1741
    - Painting the Sun Pole (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1742
    - Erecting the Sun Pole (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1743
    - Entering the Lodge (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1744
    - Buffalo Head (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1745
    - Blessing the Food (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1746
    - The Last Salute to the Sun Gods - Cheyenne Sun Dance (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1747
    - Shadows (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1748
    - Short Bull - An Old Crow Chief (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1749
    - Goes Ahead - One of Custer's Scouts (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1750
    - Mixing the Medicine Tobacco Seed (Box 6, Folder 29)
      TP1751